Now we need to talk about another important movement,
which is the neural crest movement.
There are different types of differentiations,
of induction factors.
There are factors that are purely metabolic.
There are factors that are passive.
This is after neurulation.
You have vessels that will guide the system.
And then you have everything that is genetic as well,
which is another induction factor.
to lead to the areas where the development occurred genetically.
Three main types of movements.
Let's go, prosencephalon, mesencephalon, rhombencephalon, and the spinal canal.
spinal canal.
When I have the closure of my neural tube,
I have the cells that will form the neural crest.
The cells that will create a lot of processes in the body.
There is like a flow from the back to the front, a
flow that will invade
your entire face.
So that means the face, the bone, the skin, up to the level of flattening, is
actually from the neural crest.
It is a tissue that is highly informed and informative.
Everything inside you is from the neural crest.
If all these ganglia, all these little things,
well, they show you on the face what is happening inside you.
So, you can learn to read the face, wrinkles, dark circles, colors.
First, I have this prosencephalon.
This prosencephalon will become telencephalon and diencephalon.
And so, you have a whole migration of the diencephalon.
So you have the diencephalon and the anterior mesencephalon that will migrate.
at the level of the neural crest.
So this means it’s a flow that happens like this and like this.
But before the closing of the neural tube occurs,
there was also a negative factor, as I explained this morning.
So it provided information regarding the hepatopancreatic,
thyroid, and cardiac systems.
So all of this will inform the neural crest,
which is also ectomesenchyme.
So it’s mesoderm with neural crest.
And we see here the importance of this migration, this colonization of
the neural crest
which will inform, which will give a specific quality.
But it will also have an impact on the construction of micro-vessels and micro
nerves especially.
And especially on the micro-nerves it will influence and also on the pericytes.
So it will inform, it will reconstruct.
Build support points, emergence points, endpoints.
Up to giving this embryonic force to restructure as much as possible
these processes, these micro-nerves that regrow.
But to help them, gradually.
And don’t forget, it’s at an electrical level.
And at the level of the eye, you see, it will have all the glassy side, you see, which will completely
encompass.
And give...
all this tissue here in front
which will be ectoderm,
among other things related
to this flow
mesodermic
around at the sclerotic level.